<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Games on Kat Purpy&#39;s Public Static Localhost</title>
    <link>http://example.org/games/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Games on Kat Purpy&#39;s Public Static Localhost</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 13:10:08 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/games/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cats Love Heat</title>
      <link>http://example.org/games/catsloveheat/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 13:10:08 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/games/catsloveheat/</guid>
      <description>Cats Love Heat    Description You are a ginger cat. You are cold. Find your warm place in this hardcore catformer christmas game!
Jump away your problems and most importantly&amp;hellip; don&amp;rsquo;t touch water!
Screenshots Buy this game on The game was made with an opensource fantasy console named TIC-80 (tic80.com) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Once upon a time when the Universe died</title>
      <link>http://example.org/games/ouatwtud/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 13:06:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/games/ouatwtud/</guid>
      <description>Once upon a time when the Universe died    Description It is year 87069095065082069095068079079077069068 after the Universe&amp;rsquo;s death.
The only things left is you and a hungry tribe of creatures that wish to consume you. Move things around and find the Universal peace so the Universe could be reborn once more.
Features  30+ levels! (10 in the current demo) Challenging controls (you have to use only one mouse and and two mouse buttons) Good sound design!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pyutas</title>
      <link>http://example.org/games/pyutas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 12:41:15 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/games/pyutas/</guid>
      <description>Pyutas    Description PyuTas is a game about pew pew(lazers) and insane shootouts with lazers.
You are the computer user who tries to clear his local network from the computer virus. Use your only weapon(lasers) to vaporize the infection.
Good luck!
Features  4 levels of difficulty from braindead to rip! 6 challenging levels! Responsible controls! Clear retro arcade styled graphics! Custom game engine based on MonoGame!  Screenshots Play the game for free on  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JigCube</title>
      <link>http://example.org/games/jigcube/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 12:13:09 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/games/jigcube/</guid>
      <description>JigCube    Description JigCube - absolutely brand new puzzle game about SURREALISM and THE FATE OF THE CUBE
Use tetraminos, your cursor and your MIND to beat all levels. Collect coins to unlock secret levels and secrets and secrets and secrets and secrets and secrets&amp;hellip;
Screenshots Play/Buy this game on </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
