<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Kat Purpy's Public Localhost</title><link>http://example.org/</link><description>Recent content on Kat Purpy's Public Localhost</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 17:43:53 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Super Monkey Bathtub Racing</title><link>http://example.org/games/monkeyracing/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 17:43:53 +0300</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/games/monkeyracing/</guid><description>Welcome to the Super Monkey Bathtub Racing! It is a low budget racing game created for MonoGameJam3. The results can be seen by clicking on this link.
Features 3 tracks 3 game modes S T O R Y ! accidentally good enemy AI early 2000s aesthetic! ✨ legally stolen soundtrack! Screenshots Gameplay video Footage from the jam host: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ggTfxHrL9Vg&amp;amp;t=12097s
The game begins at 31:27:21 (Sorry for inconivinience but couldn&amp;rsquo;t embed it because YouTube was being funky with timecodes)</description></item><item><title>Hello Background My Old Friend</title><link>http://example.org/blog/hello-background-my-old-friend/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2021 21:12:16 +0300</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/blog/hello-background-my-old-friend/</guid><description>The Truth about CSS filters and WebGL</description></item><item><title>Site update or How Not to Make Spicy Backgrounds That Abuse Your CPU and GPU</title><link>http://example.org/blog/how-not-to-make-spicy-backgrounds/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 00:18:26 +0300</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/blog/how-not-to-make-spicy-backgrounds/</guid><description>A short lesson on how to do things right.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>http://example.org/about/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 17:03:17 +0300</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/about/</guid><description>Yeah that's me, an anonymous content creator from deep snows of Russia.
I make games as programming excerise but sometimes I end up making good and engaging games worth playing. :p
I use Unity, MonoGame for creating said above software.
Also I make music which can be found on my soundcloud. Prepare your ears as I write mostly experimental music, some music may melt your ears, some may bless them, some may [REDACTED]</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>http://example.org/links/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 17:03:17 +0300</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/links/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Cats Love Heat</title><link>http://example.org/games/catsloveheat/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 13:10:08 +0300</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/games/catsloveheat/</guid><description>
Cats Love Heat Description You are a ginger cat. You are cold. Find your warm place in this hardcore catformer christmas game!
Jump away your problems and most importantly&amp;hellip; don&amp;rsquo;t touch water!
Screenshots Buy this game on
The game was made with an opensource fantasy console named TIC-80 (tic80.com)</description></item><item><title>Once upon a time when the Universe died</title><link>http://example.org/games/ouatwtud/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 13:06:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/games/ouatwtud/</guid><description>Once upon a time when the Universe died Description It is year 87069095065082069095068079079077069068 after the Universe&amp;rsquo;s death.
The only things left is you and a hungry tribe of creatures that wish to consume you. Move things around and find the Universal peace so the Universe could be reborn once more.
Features 30+ levels! (10 in the current demo) Challenging controls (you have to use only one mouse and and two mouse buttons) Good sound design!</description></item><item><title>Pyutas</title><link>http://example.org/games/pyutas/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 12:41:15 +0300</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/games/pyutas/</guid><description>
Pyutas Description PyuTas is a game about pew pew(lazers) and insane shootouts with lazers.
You are the computer user who tries to clear his local network from the computer virus. Use your only weapon(lasers) to vaporize the infection.
Good luck!
Features 4 levels of difficulty from braindead to rip! 6 challenging levels! Responsible controls! Clear retro arcade styled graphics! Custom game engine based on MonoGame! Screenshots Play the game for free on</description></item><item><title>JigCube</title><link>http://example.org/games/jigcube/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 12:13:09 +0300</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/games/jigcube/</guid><description>
JigCube Description JigCube - absolutely brand new puzzle game about SURREALISM and THE FATE OF THE CUBE
Use tetraminos, your cursor and your MIND to beat all levels. Collect coins to unlock secret levels and secrets and secrets and secrets and secrets and secrets&amp;hellip;
Screenshots Play/Buy this game on</description></item><item><title>Hello World</title><link>http://example.org/blog/hiworld/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 11:23:43 +0300</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/blog/hiworld/</guid><description>First ever post</description></item></channel></rss>